let coding = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",
      answer: "if condition:",
      options: ["if (condition):", "if condition", "if: condition", "if condition:"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",
      answer: "ArrayList",
      options: ["String", "Number", "Boolean", "ArrayList"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",
      answer: "int",
      options: ["var", "let", "const", "int"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",
      answer: "for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",
      options: ["for i = 0 to 10", "for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)", "for (int i = 0; i <= 10)", "for i in range(0, 10)"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",
      answer: "foreach",
      options: ["while", "for", "do-while", "foreach"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following is not a valnumb operator in C++?",
      answer: "$",
      options: ["+", "-", "*", "$"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",
      answer: "Python",
      options: ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "C++"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",
      answer: "def name()",
      options: ["function name()", "def name", "function name", "def name()"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",
      answer: "Object",
      options: ["Int", "String", "Double", "Object"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",
      answer: "C++",
      options: ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "C++"]
      
      
    },
  ];
